<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<locales>
    <groups name="pcsg/steemit-steempunk-template" datatype="php,js">
        <locale name="package.title" html="true">
            <en><![CDATA[STEEMPUNK-NET Template]]></en>
        </locale>
    </groups>

    <groups name="pcsg/steempunknet" datatype="php,js">
        <!-- template bricks -->
        <locale name="character.class.aristocrat">
            <en><![CDATA[Aristocrat]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="character.class.adventurer">
            <en><![CDATA[Adventurer]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="weapons.title">
            <en><![CDATA[Weapons and items]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="message.no.inventory">
            <en><![CDATA[You have no items at the moment :(]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="login.header">
            <en><![CDATA[Login]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="login.welcome.message" html="true">
            <en><![CDATA[
            <p>Enter the gate to a world where technology and blockchain give you unique opportunities.</p>
            ]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="login.language.message">
            <en><![CDATA[Please choose your language]]></en>
        </locale>

        <!-- Skills -->
        <locale name="skills.SPF">
            <en><![CDATA[SPF]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="skills.experience">
            <en><![CDATA[Experience]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="skills.strength">
            <en><![CDATA[Strength]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="skills.education">
            <en><![CDATA[Education]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="skills.defense">
            <en><![CDATA[Defense]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="skills.dexterity">
            <en><![CDATA[Dexterity]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="skills.constitution">
            <en><![CDATA[Constitution]]></en>
        </locale>

        <!-- nav / buttons / tabs -->
        <locale name="nav.user">
            <en><![CDATA[User]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="nav.history">
            <en><![CDATA[History]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="nav.settings">
            <en><![CDATA[Settings]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="nav.store">
            <en><![CDATA[Store]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="nav.battle">
            <en><![CDATA[Attack]]></en>
        </locale>

        <!-- History -->
        <locale name="history.upcoming.title">
            <en><![CDATA[Coming fights]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="history.done.title">
            <en><![CDATA[Struggled battles]]></en>
        </locale>

        <!-- History -->
        <locale name="settings.title">
            <en><![CDATA[Settings]]></en>
        </locale>

        <!-- History -->
        <locale name="settings.general">
            <en><![CDATA[General]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="settings.language">
            <en><![CDATA[Language]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="settings.menu">
            <en><![CDATA[Menu]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="settings.menu.open.at.steemit">
            <en><![CDATA[Open the menu automatically when steemit.com is visited the first time.]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="settings.menu.open.at.news">
            <en><![CDATA[Open the menu automatically if there are news.]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="settings.news">
            <en><![CDATA[News]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="settings.news.mail">
            <en><![CDATA[Inform me by mail if someone attacks me.]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="settings.logout">
            <en><![CDATA[Logout]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="settings.save">

            <en><![CDATA[Save settings]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="constitution.is.to.low">
            <en><![CDATA[
                The many battles of recent times have consumed your strength. You should get some rest.
            ]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="exception.fighters.handler.constitution.is.missing">
            <en><![CDATA[
                The many battles of recent times have consumed your strength. You should get some rest.
            ]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="exception.fighters.handler.constitution.is.missing.battles">
            <en><![CDATA[
                You still have [battles] battles to fight. This would consumed your strength.
            ]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="exception.fighters.handler.constitution.is.missing.battles.1">
            <en><![CDATA[
                You still have [battles] battle to fight. This would consumed your strength.
            ]]></en>
        </locale>

        <!-- welcome -->
        <locale name="welcome.button.characterSelect">
            <en><![CDATA[Start right now]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="welcome.button.about">
            <en><![CDATA[The STEEMPUNK-NET WORLD]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="welcome.character.title">
            <en><![CDATA[What are you?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="welcome.character.text">
            <en><![CDATA[
            To get started, you have to answer the simple question from the STEEMPUNK-NET consortium:
            ]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="welcome.character.gender.title">
            <en><![CDATA[Which gender do you have?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="welcome.message">
            <en><![CDATA[Welcome to the Clockwork-Arena, Steemian!]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="welcome.language.select.title">
            <en><![CDATA[Language selection]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="welcome.language.select.description">
            <en><![CDATA[Which language do you want to use?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="welcome.language.select.next">
            <en><![CDATA[Next]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="male">
            <en><![CDATA[male]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="female">
            <en><![CDATA[female]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="aristocrat">
            <en><![CDATA[Aristocrat]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="adventurer">
            <en><![CDATA[Adventurer]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="welcome.character.enter">
            <en><![CDATA[Enter the world of STEEMPUNK-NET!]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="adventurer.description" html="true">
            <en><![CDATA[
            <p>So you're one of those <strong>underworld rats</strong> who live deep in the gorges of
            Steemopolis and never see the daylight? Do you even have an access to
            the net and know what a blockchain is, you analogue? Haha!</p>

            <p>Don't look so insulted, it's just fun.
            There are plenty of rats here in the Clockwork-Arena.
            Probably the only way for you to get a couple of coins, huh?
            Okay, then just register here with your fingerprint.
            Afterwards, we will quickly place an implant for you to record your data.
            A fresh STEEMPUNK-NET-Node, guaranteed as good as new! Only used for
            <strong>the weekly combat rankings</strong>. I promise!</p>

            <p>So, and now you're ready for the brave new world out there.
            When you meet other Clockwork-Fighters in Steemit, you can <strong>challenge</strong> them.
            At the <strong>latest two hours later, the fight begins automatically</strong> here in the arena.
            No drawback possible, haha!
            You'll find out the rest for yourself. Good luck!</p>
            ]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="aristocrat.description" html="true">
            <en><![CDATA[
            <p>Forgive me, Sire, for having to ask about your origins!
            It's regulation, very strict, I'm just following orders from above.
            Well, since you are coming from the upper floors, its your rules so to speak.
            From one of the <strong>successful entrepreneurial families</strong>, I presume? One of the big multinationals?</p>

            <p>Forgive my curiosity! You certainly don't have much time and want to do your registration
            as a Clockwork-Fighter quickly. A good way to multiply your coins, sire?
            Or do you want to show it to your friends? We from the STEEMPUNK-NET consortium promise you:
            You will see parts of Steemit that will make your eyes turn!</p>

            <p>Now enough chitchat! Just register with your public key.
            After that we will quickly place an implant for you to evaluate <strong>the weekly fight rankings</strong>.
            A very fresh STEEMPUNK-NET-Node, best quality for you, Sire!</p>

            <p>All right, and now you're ready for the brave new world out there.
            If you meet Steemit with other Clockwork-Fighters, you can <strong>challenge</strong> them.
            At <strong>the latest two hours later, the fight begins automatically</strong> here in the arena.
            It is not possible to withdraw.
            Life as a Clockwork-Fighter will teach you the rest, sire. Good luck!</p>
            ]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="story.title">
            <en><![CDATA[The world of STEEMPUNK-NET]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="story" html="true">
            <en><![CDATA[
            <h2>New Powers: Multinational Corporations and Blockchains</h2>

            <p>It's the year 2279. The economy collapsed. Governments have no power anymore.
            Fiat currencies have become worthless.</p>

            <p>Instead, multinational corporations control world affairs.
            With cryptocurrencies, they have created new funds and are spending them on their loyal
            customers. What began as a utopia has long since become a means of totalitarian
            consumer surveillance. Blockchains control the lives of people in this new society.</p>

            <p>Businesses act like the states of yesteryear:
            they enact their own laws; they monitor compliance with their rules and ensure that
            offenders are punished fairly. Thanks to the sheer confusing data flows,
            multinationals know everything about the citizens - and the citizens have
            long since lost their sovereignty over their data.</p>

            <h2>New social order: At the top and bottom</h2>

            <p>Most people are hardly disturbed by these conditions.
            As they have been doing for thousands of years, they are indulging in their everyday lives.
            They give themselves up to advertising, populists and pre-chewed content,
            but they don't question anything. But some of them live differently...</p>

            <p>The aristocrats are at the very top - in the truest sense of the word.
            The elite of the new company consists of the richest entrepreneurial families and thrones
            on the highest floors of the skyscrapers of all urban megacities.
            Equipped with the latest technology, their potential for higher things is artificially
            improved before they are born - genetic optimisation, sophisticated implants,
            performance-enhancing stimulation packs.</p>

            <p>But the price for life in luxury and transhumanistic performance enhancement is high:
            young aristocrats are constantly under observation starting with the first cell division
            in the womb. Always online, always tracked, always analyzed - and the blockchain never
            forgets anything. Often it is only noticeable that you are sitting in a golden cage when
            you try to break out of it...</p>

            <p>The adventurers are at the bottom.
            In the deepest gorges of the urban Molochs they live their existence.
            The basic needs of the new and old worlds are not adequately met here.
            There is a lack of water, food, Internet access and crypto money.
            While the beautiful new world reigns in the upper floors, the lower class has lost everything:
            knowledge, possessions, culture...</p>

            <p>But instead, you have a freedom down here that the upper world can only dream of.
            Because anyone who is offline elude the all-embracing grip of the corporations.
            Here the law of the strongest - or that of the cleverest - prevails.
            Anyone who can still gain access to secure network connection can make a lot of money -
            provided you don't care about decency and morality.</p>

            <h2>New challenges: battles on the agenda</h2>

            <p>Whether up or down, aristocrat or adventurer:
            you are not like the other sheep, who follow their daily life plans. You want more!
            The STEEMPUNK-NET consortium enables organised duels between the citizens of Steemit:
            Arena and street fights, to which everyone can register.
            Each Clockwork-Fighter thus becomes a hunter and at the same time a prey.
            The fight lurks at every corner.</p>

            <p>The most successful Clockwork-Fighters will be rewarded with glory and honour
            in a weekly ranking. As rewards, coins, valuable items and ever-increasing combat
            experience are enticing. And then there is the mystery surrounding the
            Holy Private Key, which promises special prosperity in this corrupt world...</p>

            <p>Are you a rich, decadent aristocrat who uses his superhuman abilities to prove
            his superiority in duels? Or are you an impoverished,
            bagged adventurer who has to seek battle to ensure his daily survival?</p>

            <p>In the world of STEEMPUNK-NET, fate rewards the brave - or the desperate</p>
            ]]></en>
        </locale>

        <!-- Messages -->
        <locale name="message.no.upcoming.fights">
            <en><![CDATA[Phew ... no attack sighted!!]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="message.no.done.fights">
            <en><![CDATA[Unfortunately, you have not played any battles yet.]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="profile.button.attack">
            <en><![CDATA[Attack]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="profile.button.attack.go">
            <en><![CDATA[Attack!!]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="profile.button.attack.cancel">
            <en><![CDATA[Oh, no, I don't think so.]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="attack.message.title">
            <en><![CDATA[Ready for the battle?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.1">
            <en><![CDATA[Are you sure you want to challenge [username]?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.2">
            <en><![CDATA[Are you ready for the battle against [username]?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.3">
            <en><![CDATA[Are you ready for the duel with [username]]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.4">
            <en><![CDATA[Do you really want to challenge[username]?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.5">
            <en><![CDATA[Do you want to ask [username] to fight?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.6">
            <en><![CDATA[Do you want to challenge [username] to a duel?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.7">
            <en><![CDATA[You want to attack [username]?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.8">
            <en><![CDATA[Do you want to fight [username]?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.9">
            <en><![CDATA[Do you want to duel with [username]?]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.10">
            <en><![CDATA[Please confirm that you want to challenge [username].]]></en>
        </locale>
        <locale name="attack.message.11">
            <en><![CDATA[If you challenge [username], there is no turning back. Are you sure about this?]]></en>
        </locale>

        <locale name="agb.button.confirm">
            <en><![CDATA[I hereby confirm that I have read and understood the Terms and Conditions]]></en>
        </locale>

    </groups>
</locales>
